# Raymond Luk

Bayside, NY 11361

Phone: (631)338-1096 Email: RLUK88@GMAIL.COM

Skilled and experienced NYC special inspector with 9+ years of experience in the construction industry. Proven track record of ensuring compliance with latest building code standards. Strong attention to detail and ability to identify and report defects. Excellent communication and interpersonal skills, with the ability to work effectively with clients, contractors, and design applicants.

## **Employment**

AK Engineering, PC, New York, NY

October 2014- July 2023

Senior Field Inspector/ Project Manager/ Technical Director

- Managed non-conformance logs and communicated with the entire project team to ensure the best and most straightforward solution to deficiencies, and completion of work.
- Maintained coordination and communication with applicable parties to ensure adherence of plans and building code.
- Proficient in reading construction documents and specifications.
- Examined equipment functional performances and provided recommendations for design engineer review.
- Developed and executed commissioning plans, functional performance testing checklists and reports for HVAC, electrical, and plumbing systems.
- Facilitated discussions for IAS accreditation for AK Engineering

DealerTrack Technologies, Lake Success, New York

August 2013 - October 2014

Desktop Client Services Technician

- Maintained strong technical support and worked directly with clients on a regular basis.
- Created and maintained knowledge base documenting methods, user training and workflow procedures.
- Maintained and managed inventory, ensuring that all equipment was in good working order.
- Organized and managed technology requests for on-boarding and off-boarding of team members.

Design Strategy Corporation, New York, New York

July 2010 - August 2013

- I.T. consultant
  - Provided technical support for corporate-wide broadcasts, events, meetings, conferences.
  - Responsible for PC migration, installation and configuration of desktop PC's, PC deactivation.
  - Identified and resolved hardware and software related issues, ensuring client satisfaction.

### **Industry Accreditations:**

ICC Commercial Mechanical Inspector	Cert # 8320414
ICC Structural Masonry Special Inspector	Cert # 8320414
ICC Steel and Bolting Special Inspector	Cert # 8320414
ACI Concrete Field Testing Technician – Grade I	ACI # 1348754
ACI Concrete Construction Special Inspector	ACI # 1348754
ACI Adhesive Anchor Installation Inspector	ACI # 1348754
Osha 30-hour Construction Safety and Health	34-602078656
ICC Steel Welding Inspector	Pending

#### Education

New York Institute of Technology Old Westbury, New York 2011

Advanced Certificate in Energy Technology

New York Institute of Technology Old Westbury, New York

2008-2011 Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering

**SUNY Binghamton** Binghamton, New York

2006-2008

## References upon request